



## ABOUT ME @

Digital visual design for web, apps. social media, client-facing marketing materials to internal communications

Critical design thinking with 'persona' research and mindset on how content design correlates with UX/UI engagement

Device inclusive: able to design for large monitors, tablets to phones - responsive design; experience in colour, typography to layouts













Photoshop

Illustrator

**AfterEffects** 











ceros





**CEROS** 

present

## **EDUCATION**

March 2017 - Jun 2017

**General Assembly** 

Web Development

> Web Development

Immersive progam

**Program** 

Sep 1998 - Apr 2002 **Toronto Metropolitan University** 

B.A.A. - Fashion Design Degree

(formerly Ryerson University)

> Fashion Design, Fashion Marketing, Consumer Product Design, Graphic Design

Jan 2001 - Aug 2001 Birmingham City University

## **Design and Merchandising**

> Selected by TMU to partake in Birmingham, UK exchange program - during second semester of third year

August 2000

**UAL: Central Saint Martins** 

## Experimentational **Design Course**

> Experimentational design course in non-conventional materials and concepts Instructor: Designer Roland Mouret

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

more on LinkedIn



#### Borden Ladner Gervais LLP • Senior Designer, Digital & Multimedia • Jan 2020 - Feb 2024

2001

2002

- > Designing digital visuals and products for <u>BLG</u> and subsidiary legal services <u>BLG Beyond</u>; landing pages, social media graphics; balancing quality, speed, accuracry and consistency in exceeding brand standards and objectives
- > Relationships with lawyers, partners, articling students, designers, business development professionals, directors, leaders; acted as BLG Affinity group regional committee member (2021 - 2023)



#### Blake, Cassels & Graydon LLP • Digital Designer • Aug 2017 - Jan 2020

> Providing digital assets for launch of blakes.com, landing pages, client-facing marketing materials, internal communications, social media channels to print materials



#### Thinkway Toys • Design Manager, Consumer Products • Apr 2016 - Mar 2017

> Design Manager in licensed consumer products including Lucas Films Ltd. (Star Wars Rogue One), Disney/ Pixar (Cars 3) and Universal Studios (Despicable Me 3)



## Disney Consumer Products (Disney Canada) • Associate, Online Product Approval • Nov 2013 - Mar 2016

- > Creative guidance with Disney OPA team in the design and development of consumer softlines and hardlines products sold across Canada, including Walmart, Target, Canadian Tire, Dollarama and Toy R' Us
- > Working with team in leading 50+ licensees on 500+ products seasonally including Frozen and disney/ pixar properties. Managing online product design approvals and meeting with vendors & licensees on communicating design goals, brand guides and defining brand initiatives

#### DOLCE & GABBANA

#### Dolce & Gabbana (Milan, Italy) | Associate • Feb 2013 - Sept 2013

> Brought 10 years of design experience abroad and resulted in an opportunity with Dolce & Gabbana in Milan; prepared and assistant with team on Fall 2013 and Spring 2014 RTW collections